<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David An</title>
    <link>https://davidan.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David An</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://davidan.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/news/</guid>
      <description>News Archive [01-15-2022]
I recently returned back to my high school to talk about my experiences and some of my tips after 2 years in college [12-05-2022]
I was invited onto the Innovations @ Research Park Podcast to talk about my recent experiences working at the University of Illinois Research Park over the summer at Ameren. Listen to the podcast. [08-15-2022]
Over the summer, me and some other friends organized a Summer of Side Projects Initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/ens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/ens/</guid>
      <description>Deploying a Naming System (Ethereum Naming System) on a Private Network This passage was taken from a GitHub repository which no longer exists and is simply on here for reference purpose
We will cover the following: ​
Basic ENS architecture Setting up ENS: Deploying the registry, registrar, and resolver contracts Writing to ENS: Registering a name and storing data Reading data from ENS, both on- and off-chain ​ 1. Introduction to the ENS architecture Before going into the technical details, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly recap how the ENS contracts work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/uiuctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/uiuctf/</guid>
      <description>UIUCTF23 Challenge Writeups! A long overdue set of writeups (solutions) for UIUCTF23. Recently I had the opportunity to help run UIUCTF 2023, a student-run capture the flag (CTF) event with some awesome folk in SIGPwny. The part I worked on mainly centered around open source intelligence (OSINT) techniques. In this post, we go over some solutions to the OSINT suite as some tips and tricks to approaching these challenges in CTFs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/professional/ameren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/professional/ameren/</guid>
      <description>Data Scientist Intern @ Ameren Innovation Center ⚡️Check back for updates on the awesome things I&amp;rsquo;m doing at Ameren&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/professional/asa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/professional/asa/</guid>
      <description>Business Analyst @ D.NEXT Lab 🚚 Check back later for some cool things I did at D.NEXT! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/research/fadenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/research/fadenet/</guid>
      <description>FaDe-Net [Writeup] David An - AP Research Project
Abstract The rapid development of social media and online news outlets has accelerated the spread of fake news across the internet. The accessibility and convenience of social media has further driven the drastic change of information consumption. As a consequence, fake news has become a significant concern because of 1) its inevitable exposure to large populations and 2) the potential to cause significant damage in modern society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/research/nlpsearch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/research/nlpsearch/</guid>
      <description>Building an NLP-Powered Repository for Cyber Risk Literature [Poster] David An, Linfeng Zheng, Zhiyu (Frank) Quan
Abstract With the large and growing body of cyber risk literature, we see three major challenges faced by the actuarial research community: there is no context aware tool for finding cyber literature, no central repository of cyber risk resources, and a lack of accounting of literature trends. To address the abovementioned challenges, we propose to build a repository of cyber-risk articles with an NLP powered search tool that can easily be used by researchers to find relevant materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/research/uconnscrape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/research/uconnscrape/</guid>
      <description>Scraping Web Data for Academic Literature Done in collaboration with Dr. Emiliano Valdez1, University of Connecticut
Goals How obvious are actual trends in academic literature and how can we easily gather academic literature metadata? The purpose of the exploratory study was to develop and analyze different methods of data retrieval from multiple sources.
Given a text search within context, we should be able to retrieve a list of articles that contain that segment of text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3,000 Miles of Solitude</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/bike/</guid>
      <description>3,000 Miles of Solitude The streets are empty with the streetlights being the only company in the morning. Wet, damp fog provide the only relief in what is projected to be another scorching day when the sun comes up. I can&amp;rsquo;t see the crows screeching into the dawn, but I can hear them singing their song.
It&amp;rsquo;s July in central Illinois. I lace up my white bike cleats, marred with grease marks and mud and clip into my bike; providing a stark contrast to the hot-rod red paint job of my carbon fiber contraptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Semester of Research</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/firstsem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/firstsem/</guid>
      <description>A Semester of Research All of this comes together for a Fake Detection Network, or FaDe-Net. In order to validate and benchmark our results, we performed a series of metric tests on the MIT Fake News Dataset1 and achieved a precision rate of 90.31% as well as an accuracy rate of 88.56%. Our experiments indicate the model is more effective at fake news detection. However, this model still has a significant amount of room to improve in future research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>Email: davidzhongtaian(at)gmail(dot)com
Linkedin: @davidzan
Talks + Presentations [05-23-2023] Women in Computer Science Summer Opportunities! Slides [04-30-2023] SIGPwny Open Source INTelligence (OSINT) Presentation Slides [04-19-2023] CS222: Software Design Lab Seminar Slides [10-03-2022] Disruption Lab Recruiting Seminar Slides [09-16-2022] CS 100: Computer Science Orientation Talk Slides [08-16-2022] Building Community in Online Learning (iCSTW 2022) Slides, Recording News Features Fortune: Snap’s ‘My AI’ chatbot tells users it doesn’t know their location. Link Research Park Innovations Podcast Episode Link Research Park Outstanding Undergraduate Intern Award Link Research + Side Fun Natural Phenomena of Roots of Cubics in the Complex Field Paper The Influence of Lunch Items on Cryptocurrency in the United States Paper Building an NLP-Powered Repository for Cyber Risk Literature Poster, Link Scraping Web Data for Academic Literature Link Volunteering + Teaching IEEE Region 5 Diversity Equity and Inclusion Committee Feb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adversial AI and ChatGPT, Examples From the Wild</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/gpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/gpt/</guid>
      <description>Adversial AI and Attacking Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s My AI UPDATE: This article was covered in the Fortune Magazine article &amp;ldquo;Snap’s ‘My AI’ chatbot tells users it doesn’t know their location. It does.&amp;rdquo; on 04-21-23!
A short excursion into the craze of ChatGPT In this article, we cover a basic introduction into LLMs, ChatGPT, and a real life example of Snapchat.
ChatGPT, the newest craze in a series of innovations regarding artificial intelligence. It seems like every day we hear about a new piece of software released.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/blog/</guid>
      <description>Random Thoughts Some excursions into different spaces. I occasionally write about math and computers.
Life For the Past 3 Months! 08-06-2023 UIUCTF&#39;23 OSINT Writeups 07-04-2023 Adversial AI and Attacking Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s My AI 04-19-2023 3,000 Miles of Solitude 04-03-2023 The Influence of Lunch Items on Crypto 03-24-2023 Jenkins Security Vulnerability Writeup 02-02-2023 A Discussion on Pandas and Data Mining 01-17-2023 Revisiting a Summer of Side Projects 12-16-2022 Inequality Fun and Their Applications 12-14-2022 A (Fun) Discussion on Harmonic Functions 12-03-2022 Donuts 11-12-2022 Unification in Academic Literature 07-07-2022 A Semester of Research 06-15-2022 Building an NLP-Powered Repository for Cyber Risk Literature 05-13-2022 Scraping Web Data for Academic Literature 02-01-2022 Fake News Detection: Using NLP in the Detection Process (FaDe-Net) 05-12-2021 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bugs</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/bugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/bugs/</guid>
      <description>Bug Reports Got bored so here is a running of list of reports and finds in my spare time. All were found accidentally and reported to their respective security groups immediately.
Organization Find Date Cloudera In progress, reported on 1-28. The fix and patch is still in progress. 1-28 AllenAI An exposed localhost port allows an actor to access production builds as an elevated user. No user authentication deployment and configuration of builds as a non-admin user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donuts</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/donut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/donut/</guid>
      <description>Donuts &amp;ldquo;$7.13 is your total sir.&amp;rdquo;
These are the same words I hear every Friday morning from the woman behind the counter. Her eyes weary from the same cycle day over day; something that has become a habit over years of monotony. However, it’s not her which gives the donut shop the character it possesses; instead, it’s moreso the cacophony of hearing the ovens blaring, cash registers ringing, and blenders blending which gives this donut shop its character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun with Inequalities</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/inequalities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/inequalities/</guid>
      <description>Inequality Fun and Their Applications This article assumes the reader has basic knowledge of calculus and analysis. Covers topics ranging from basic Cauchy Schwarz to Lipschitz, culminating in us pulling out a mathematical rabbit out of an algebraic hat.
1. What is an Inequality? An inequality compares two values, showing if one is less than, greater than, or simply not equal to another value. Literally, it does not get more simpler than that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmonic Functions</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/harmonic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/harmonic/</guid>
      <description>A (Fun) Discussion on Harmonic Functions Some introductions into harmonic functions. This post is meant to be an approchable read into these phenomena.
1. Introduction on Harmonic Functions A mass on a spring, measuring fluid flow, even the cosine wave, are all examples of where harmonic functions can be found within our world. The name itself stems from an object or force going through some type of harmonic (or oscillating) motion from a steady state equilibrium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Many Chairs? Excursions into Fermi Questions</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/fermi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/fermi/</guid>
      <description>Fermi Questions and Chairs on Campus (WIP) How many chairs are there really on campus?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenkins Security Vulnerability Writeup</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/pwn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/pwn/</guid>
      <description>Jenkins Security Vulnerability Writeup So, how does it begin? After getting bored one day and browsing Shodan.io, one wonders what&amp;rsquo;s the worst that you can find on there? Turns out, the answer led to a 2-day bender down different rabbit holes eventually leading to this article here and a lot of vulnerabilities discovered. So let&amp;rsquo;s get started shall we?
Before we do this, I do not endorse attempting to break into company systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life For the Past 3 Months</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/catchup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/catchup/</guid>
      <description>Life For the Past 3 Months It&amp;rsquo;s been 2.5 months since I graduated, and approximately 3-ish months since the last computer or mathematical related post. While alot has gone on, there will definitely be a steady catch up of content that has been written but not yet uploaded. After settling down and moving, there should be much more time to write. In lieu of that however, there has been alot of time to do cool things and catch up with people since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch and Crypto</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/bovik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/bovik/</guid>
      <description>The Influence of Lunch Items on Cryptocurrency in the United States *This post is pending for SIGBOVIK 0x7e7*
For some background information, SIGBOVIK is a yearly scientific conference hosted by Carnegie Mellon University where participants are able to flex their lesser-known research muscles. These are the dank-memers of academia.
Abstract In this paper, we introduce the discovery and exploration of the influence of common every day lunch items on cryptocurrency trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandas and Data Mining</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/datamining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/datamining/</guid>
      <description>A Discussion on Pandas and Data Mining At the beginning of any data analytics/data science project, the most usual case is utilizing Pandas to load the data into a object called a DataFrame and perform preprocessing tasks on it. While the Pandas library is convenient and comes with a trove of useful analytic tools, it does have some inefficiencies, many due to the nature of Python. To investigate this, let&amp;rsquo;s look at how Pandas actually works on top of Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/sitemap/</guid>
      <description>Fun Stuff R-Guide For Statistics Summer of Side Projects 2022 Guide to Research Park 1.0 Blog Adversial AI and Attacking Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s My AI 3,000 Miles of Solitude The Influence of Lunch Items on Crypto Jenkins Security Vulnerability Writeup A Discussion on Pandas and Data Mining A Discussion on Pandas and Data Mining (WIP) Revisiting a Summer of Side Projects Inequality Fun and Their Applications A (Fun) Discussion on Harmonic Functions Donuts The need for a unified cataloging system for academic literature Looking back on a semester of undergraduate research Research D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer of Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/sosp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/sosp/</guid>
      <description>Revisiting a Summer of Side Projects This is a long overdue writeup with open source learning and Summer of Side Projects 2022 &amp;ldquo;Go do a project.&amp;rdquo;
Sure, that’s what everyone talks about and describes as the optimal way to break into the tech space. Nowadays, tech seems to be all the rage, co-inflating into this large bubble of glamorous perks and lifestyles. Silicon Valley and other areas have become the new meccas for innovation, all sought after by anyone who wants to go into big tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beauty of Polynomials</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/polynomial1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/polynomial1/</guid>
      <description>Cubic Polynomials and their Beauty </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unification in Academic Literature</title>
      <link>https://davidan.dev/posts/unified/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidan.dev/posts/unified/</guid>
      <description>Unification in Academic Literature Libraries store the energy that fuels the imagination. They open up windows to the world and inspire us to explore and acheive, and contribute to improving our quality of life -Sidney Sheldon
Chaos is always present. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s in the weather or in crowds, things always tend to be in disarray. The same can be said for data storage and retrieval systems as well.
The concept of data is odd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
